There are
two ways to add new events to your site.
The first is by going to dashboard
and going to your events
block and clicking Add.
The second is by going to your calendar.
And at the top clicking add an event.
List.
First we need to give our event the title.
You say when the event is on.
We're
going to get back to that in a second.
And then we need to add a body
for the event.
We can add tags to the event if we like.
We can add multiple tags.
And existing tags.
Or say we want to add this for the 2526
school year.
We can also add a calendar.
You can ignore this also if you want to.
But it is a way to, group
your calendars together.
So I don't know
if we have any calendars in here,
so let's
see if you have any existing calendars.
Just the basic calendar.
So let's add a new calendar.
This is.
Choose a color.
It doesn't really matter.
This is just a color
that it shows up on the
on the calendar.
Create that.
Okay, so let's get back to
the time of the event.
The time of the event can be very simple
or it can be very complicated.
A simple event
might take place on one day at one time.
So we can just choose.
6 to 7 for an hour on the 25th.
See that?
And if we go to the 25th there, we see it.
We can also have events
that span multiple days.
So this is our day event.
And it's going to take place from the 25th
through the 31st.
Let's see what that looks like.
We see the purple color we had.
Another type of events
is repeating events.
So let's say that
this is a play that we're going to put on
every Saturday
at 6 p.m.
until 8:00 pm.
And we are going to repeat this weekly
every one week.
And we're going to end after.
Four events.
Oops.
It's Google Calendar,
but we can also see here.
That our dates
are showing up in the actual event.
And if we go back to the calendar.
We can see
Peter Pan, Peter Pan, Peter Pan.
And Peter Pan.
The last and maybe
most complicated way to do
this is multiple
unrelated, events.
So I'm going to start
with a new event for this.
And let's say this is, this is,
For teacher meetings.
And they're going to be kind
of a little bit
sporadic. So.
From 4 to 6 on the 20th
to add another date
on the 21st.
It's also going to be for.
Two six.
But then on
Thursday
it's going to be a short one
7 to 8.
So probably
somebody.
You know, normally this would be a link.
I don't really have one prepared,
so I'll just.
With Google.
Again we can add tabs.
We can add it to calendars.
And now for this one
I go to our events.
We're going to see
parent teacher parent teacher.
And on Thursday parent teacher.
If I view any one of these events,
I can see
all of the times that it takes place.
To edit event.
Just like, I didn't do anything else.
We can go to the actual
event page and click edit.
We can edit what's here.
We have our revisions
that I covered in the,
news message section.
We could add it to calendars. Now.
We could create tags if we wanted to.
And if we're done, we just click save.